

CONTACT



Pune



chandanshivemanoj@gmail.com



+91 9595663398

EDUCATIONS

2020 : Ethical Hacking (Course) Udemy & Hacking flix, Online

2016 : Digital Marketing (Course) School Of Digital Marketing, Pune

2013-15: Masters In Business Administration (MBA), Sinhgad Institute, Pune

2010-13: BA in Geography, DBF Dayanand College, Solapur

2006-09: SSC & HSC, Nagnath Jr College, Mohol

TECHNICAL SKILL

- Search Engine Optimization SEO
- Search Engine Marketing
- Social Media Marketing
- Email Marketing
- Kali Linux Tools
- Computer Forensics Investigation
- Website penetration testing
- Ethical Hacking & Cyber Security
- Metasploit
- Darknet & Deepweb

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Best Employee Award
 (Re-enact, Pushpam Group)
- Certified Digital Marketer
- · Certified Ethical Hacker
- Google AdWords Certified
- Google Analytics Certified

MANOJ V. CHANDANSHIVE

Digital Marketing Strategist | Lead Generation Expert | Brand Building | Ethical Hacker | MarTech |

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Result Oriented **Digital Marketer** with 5+ years of experience in areas of National and International projects dealing with B2B and B2C Market, with solid knowledge of **online marketing** tools and current digital marketing channels. Looking for a new challenging role to utilize my knowledge & experience to achieve organizational as well as personal goals.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Pushpam Group of Companies : May 2017 – Present Designation : Digital Marketing Head

- Taking care of agency business.
- Leading and managing the digital marketing team.
- Creating marketing and communications strategy & action plan.
- Plan and administer monthly budget for all digital & online marketing activities to keep cost in control.
- Work closely with sales, development, content writers and other teams.
- Multiple campaign management and optimization.
- Publishing monthly and quarterly reports to stakeholders & clients.
- Assigning the work to the team & collecting the reports.
- Analyse clicks and conversion data, ad expenses and CPA.
- Understanding analytics and measuring ROI.
- Building up High-performance team.
- Coaching, imparting training on marketing techniques to the team for enhanced performance.

SME Networks Pvt Ltd: August 2016 – February 2017 Designation: Digital Marketing Specialist

- · Google Ads & Social Media Management
- Making strategies for on-page and off-page optimization.
- Doing Keywords Research, Preparing Content Strategy and Content Marketing
- Preparing traffic report using Google Analytics & Webmaster.
- Implementing different social media and SEO strategies to attract the target audience.
- Generating organic leads through joining Facebooks and LinkedIn groups
- Coordinate and work with higher management for execution of the Final project.
- Responsible for overall digital marketing activities

Ariel Outdoors Advertising Designation : Marketing Manager

- Responsible for developing executing the business development plan/Sales Plan
- Generation of new business leads/clients and retention of the existing clients.
- Responsible to convert conversations into the appointments with potential clients.
- Making outbound calls and lead generation.
- Achievement of sales targets through effective business development.
- Develop strategies & implementation strategies, Market Research to maximize services depth revenue opportunities.
- Develop the monthly, quarterly & annual business development plan that reflects the right balance.
- Conduct face to face calls with customers as well as prospects pr
- Responsible for selling services/products line by thoroughly assessing
- Minute and circulate all discussions/briefs/ information, post client meetings and telephonic or email interactions with the client.